So you can start this course by understanding RFID concepts, which are in Section one, and we are
going to see what type of RFID cards we are going to use.
Right.
So all the things which are necessary, we will cover in understanding RFID.
Then there is quick overview of Arduino.
After that, we will utilize Arduino and we will try to get the Uuid of Mifare classic RFID cards.
In Section three.
In Section four, we are going to understand the complete memory structure of Mifare classic cards.
And in Section five, we are going to program RFID cards using ACR 1 to 2 you tool and we will see what
are sectors and blocks and how we are going to program these sectors and blocks.
In section six, we are going to program the same classic card, but this time we will use a different
tool.
And the tool is known as MFC 5 to 2 with STM eight microcontroller.
So you can use either ACR 1 to 2 or you can also use MFC 5 to 2 two with eight microcontroller In section
seven, we are going to see how we can find vulnerabilities in Mifare classic card using prox Mark three
and we are also going to see how we can clone these Mifare classic cards.
In section eight.
We are going to utilize all our knowledge in our final project.
We will try to create an industry standard project in section eight.
So either you can proceed in the same manner as it is shown over here, or you can also proceed in this
manner in which you can first understand the RFID concept.
Then you can understand the method, classic card memory structure, and then you can try to program
using ACR one, two, 2 or 5 2223522.
With STM eight microcontroller, I would recommend that you should follow this method in which you first
understand the RFID concepts and then you can.
And then you can understand the memory structure of RFID cards.
And then you should program these cards.
And after that you can go through quick overview of Arduino and then you can utilize Arduino to get
the Uid.
After that, you can see the vulnerabilities using prox mark three and then you can use all the knowledge
in your final project.
So this is the recommended method in which you should first go to section one, then section four,
five, six, then you can go through section two, three, seven and eight.
So whatever method is convenient to you, you can go through it.
It is just the matter of your own convenience, right?